{
    "subject": "Isabella_of_Angoul\u00eame",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "John_of_England",
    "human_readable": "Isabella of Angoul\u00eame is married to John of England.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9877921938896179,
            "question": "Is there a marriage between Isabella of Angoul\u00eame and John of England?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9730537533760071,
            "question": "Who are the spouses in this relationship: Isabella of Angoul\u00eame and John of England?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9712375402450562,
            "question": "Was Isabella of Angoul\u00eame in a relationship with John of England?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9410296082496643,
            "question": "Who is Isabella of Angoul\u00eame married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9342960715293884,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Isabella of Angoul\u00eame and John of England?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8618015050888062,
            "question": "To whom was Isabella of Angoul\u00eame wed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8120347261428833,
            "question": "Who was John of England married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8120347261428833,
            "question": "Who was John of England married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.787175178527832,
            "question": "What is the name of Isabella of Angoul\u00eame's husband?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6058966517448425,
            "question": "What is the name of John of England's wife?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Isabella of Angoul\u00eame is married to John of England.",
            "html": "yago_27913_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Isabella of Angoul\u00eame's husband?",
            "html": "yago_27913_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who was John of England married to?",
            "html": "yago_27913_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who was John of England married to?",
            "html": "yago_27913_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27913_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27913_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27913_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27913_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27913_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27913_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27913_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27913_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27913_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27913_82.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the provided context information, I can conclude that:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents mention Isabella of Angoul\u00eame as the second wife of King John, which supports the triple statement."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe context information provided supports the statement that \"Isabella of Angoul\u00eame is married to John of England.\" The documents explicitly mention her marriage to King John, also referred to as \"John Lackland of England,\" and provide details about this union, including its commencement on 24 August 1200."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}